(Howard:)In your supercooled
helium experiments,
(Howard:)did you create
quantum vortices?
(Leonard:)Yeah. Why?
(Howard:)Well, if you made
a guidance system,
(Howard:)couldn't you use those vortices
as a gyroscope?
(Leonard:)Wow. I've never thought
about that.
(Howard:)And since
it's in a quantum state,
(Howard:)it would maintain
an infinite persistence.
(Raj:)Groundbreaking revelations,
tropical drinks.
(Raj:)Tell me this isn't like the best
episode of Sex and the City.
(Leonard:)You may have actually
just come up with something.
(Howard:)You think so?
I really do.
(Sheldon:)You guys, the bathroom
here is amazing.
(Sheldon:)There's people
cooking in it.
(Amy:)Think about all the fun
things you get to do
(Amy:)when you have a baby.
Yeah!
(Penny:)Yeah, you get to buy toys
and little clothes.
(Bernadette:)I kind of already do that
for Howie.
And-and whenever you're hungry,
(Penny:)you'll be in a minivan with
Cheerios all over the floor.
(Amy:)Oh, and I just found a
new travel cup for Sheldon.
(Amy:)It only lets out
three at a time.
(Amy:)So, when did you guys
decide to get pregnant?